Women's Center Records UA156
Tufts Archival Research Center
- Office files, 1972 -- 2007; UA156.001; 9.4 Linear Feet; 16 Digital Object(s)
  - [Articles], 2000; UA156.001.003.00037 (Box 3)
  - [Peggy Barrett's appointment book], 1997; UA156.001.003.00038 (Box 3)
  - Orientation packet - Women's Center information, 2000; UA156.001.003.00039 (Box 3)
  - Dessert night, 1995 -- 1996; UA156.001.003.00040 (Box 3)
  - Orientation - misc events, 1996; UA156.001.003.00041 (Box 3)
  - Contact info and miscellaneous [1 of 2] - contacts / other people interested, 2000; UA156.001.003.00042 (Box 3)
  - Contact info and miscellaneous [2 of 2] - websites / to email, 2000; UA156.001.003.00043 (Box 3)
  - Black women's group [1 of 3] - correspondence and contacts, 2000; UA156.001.003.00044 (Box 3)
  - Black women's group [2 of 3] - BWG topics of interest, 2000; UA156.001.003.00045 (Box 3)
  - Black women's group [3 of 3] - Meetings / notes, 2000 -- 2001; UA156.001.003.00046 (Box 3)
  - Women's Center, 2001; UA156.001.003.00047 (Box 3)
  - Film series, 2001 -- 2002; UA156.001.003.00048 (Box 3)
  - Advertising [1 of 2] - ASAP - pens, buttons, 2000; UA156.001.003.00049 (Box 3)
  - Advertising [2 of 2] - tabling, 2000; UA156.001.003.00050 (Box 3)
  - Women's Center board [1 of 4] - correspondence, 2000; UA156.001.003.00051 (Box 3)
  - Women's Center board [2 of 4] - meetings - women's board, 1999 -- 2000; UA156.001.003.00052 (Box 3)
  - Women's Center board [3 of 4] - meeting agendas fall / spring, 2000 -- 2001; UA156.001.003.00053 (Box 3)
  - Women's Center board [4 of 4] - members, fall-spring, 2000 -- 2001; UA156.001.003.00054 (Box 3)
  - To do [1 of 3] - filing, 2001; UA156.001.003.00055 (Box 3)
  - To do [2 of 3] - reading material, 2000; UA156.001.003.00056 (Box 3)
  - To do [3 of 3] - currrent lists, 2001; UA156.001.003.00057 (Box 3)
  - Database master list and alpha list, 2002; UA156.001.003.00058 (Box 3)
  - Alumni database files Kristin Hooper, 2002; UA156.001.003.00059 (Box 3)
  - Video orders, 2001; UA156.001.003.00060 (Box 3)
  - [Events], 2001; UA156.001.003.00061 (Box 3)
  - Vagina Monologues (Sun, Feb. 18), 2000 -- 2001; UA156.001.003.00062 (Box 3)
  - Budget, 2000 -- 2001; UA156.001.003.00063 (Box 3)
  - Open house, 2000; UA156.001.003.00064 (Box 3)
  - Meetings with Peggy, 2000; UA156.001.003.00065 (Box 3)
  - Tufts Daily, 2000 -- 2001; UA156.001.003.00066 (Box 3)
  - A Long Walk Home, 2000 -- 2001; UA156.001.003.00067 (Box 3)
  - [Fliers and pamphlets], 1997 -- 2006; UA156.001.003.00068 (Box 3)
  - [Student sexual assault, 1 of 7], 2003; UA156.001.003.00069 (Box 3)
  - [Student sexual assault, 2 of 7] - student concerns, 2004; UA156.001.003.00070 (Box 3)
  - [Student sexual assault, 3 of 7], 2005; UA156.001.003.00071 (Box 3)
  - [Student sexual assault, 4 of 7], 2003 -- 2004; UA156.001.003.00072 (Box 3)
  - [Student sexual assault, 5 of 7], 2004; UA156.001.003.00073 (Box 3)
  - [Student sexual assault, 6 of 7] - data collection / cases, 2003; UA156.001.003.00074 (Box 3)
  - [Student sexual assault, 7 of 7] - cases, 2003; UA156.001.003.00075 (Box 3)
  - Auction, 2001; UA156.001.004.00001 (Box 4)
  - [Club Europa Sinful flier], 2001; UA156.001.004.00002 (Box 4)
  - Mr. Jumbo pageants, 2003; UA156.001.004.00003 (Box 4)
  - Speaker contact information, 2004; UA156.001.004.00004 (Box 4)
  - Students interested, 2003 -- 2004; UA156.001.004.00005 (Box 4)
  - Peer education - discussion ideas, 2004; UA156.001.004.00006 (Box 4)
  - Current programs [1 of 4] - summer, 2000; UA156.001.004.00007 (Box 4)
  - Current programs [2 of 4 - meeting], 1999; UA156.001.004.00008 (Box 4)
    Original title reads: Current programs - stu mtg c mel
  - Current programs [3 of 4] - program ideas, 1998 -- 2003; UA156.001.004.00009 (Box 4)
  - Current programs [4 of 4] - program ideas, 2000 -- 2001; UA156.001.004.00010 (Box 4)
  - Program ideas, 2000; UA156.001.004.00011 (Box 4)
  - [Student Sexual Assault Response Assistance] schedule, 2004 -- 2005; UA156.001.004.00012 (Box 4)
    Original title reads: SSARA schedule.
  - Take Back the Night, 1996 -- 2000; UA156.001.004.00013 (Box 4)
  - Course, 2005; UA156.001.004.00014 (Box 4)
  - Bob Burdick, 2000; UA156.001.004.00015 (Box 4)
  - Programs - building multi-racial alliances, 2004 -- 2005; UA156.001.004.00016 (Box 4)
  - Student groups [1 of 5 - Women's Center board], 2003 -- 2004; UA156.001.004.00017 (Box 4)
    Original title reads: Student groups - women's board.
  - Student groups [2 of 5 - Women's Center board], 2003; UA156.001.004.00018 (Box 4)
    Original title reads: Student groups - WC board 2003/4
  - Student groups [3 of 5 - Women's Center board] - week, 2003; UA156.001.004.00019 (Box 4)
    Original title reads: Student groups - WC board/week 2003
  - Student groups [4 of 5] - Women's Center board, 2000 -- 2002; UA156.001.004.00020 (Box 4)
  - Student groups [5 of 5] - Black Women's Group, 1998 -- 2000; UA156.001.004.00021 (Box 4)
  - Programs - Viewpoint, 2004 -- 2005; UA156.001.004.00022 (Box 4)
  - Rape Education Group, 1999; UA156.001.004.00023 (Box 4)
  - Graduate students, 1998 -- 2000; UA156.001.004.00024 (Box 4)
  - SG - photo class, 2004; UA156.001.004.00025 (Box 4)
  - Leaders - women - targeting, 1997; UA156.001.004.00026 (Box 4)
  - [National Organization for Men Against Sexism], 2000; UA156.001.004.00027 (Box 4)
    Original title reads: NOMAS
  - [Student groups, 1 of 3] - Tufts Men Against Violence, 1997 -- 2002; UA156.001.004.00028 (Box 4)
  - [Student groups, 2 of 3] - Eating Disorder Group, 2002; UA156.001.004.00029 (Box 4)
  - [Student groups, 3 of 3 - Eating Disorder Group], 2003 -- 2004; UA156.001.004.00030 (Box 4)
  - Feminist Alliance, 1997 -- 2003; UA156.001.004.00031 (Box 4)
  - Vagina Monologues, 2001 -- 2003; UA156.001.004.00032 (Box 4)
  - Vagina Monologues, 2001; UA156.001.004.00033 (Box 4)
  - Peer education, 2001; UA156.001.004.00034 (Box 4)
  - Peer education, 2000 -- 2001; UA156.001.004.00035 (Box 4)
  - Peer education, 1999 -- 2000; UA156.001.004.00036 (Box 4)
  - Peer education, 1998; UA156.001.004.00037 (Box 4)
  - Peer education [fliers], 1998; UA156.001.004.00038 (Box 4)
  - Peer education - marketing, 1999; UA156.001.004.00039 (Box 4)
  - Peer education - schedules, 1999; UA156.001.004.00040 (Box 4)
  - Concepts of Beauty booklet, 1998 -- 1999; UA156.001.004.00041 (Box 4)
  - [Eating Disorder Group, 1 of 2] - eating committee, 1998 -- 2001; UA156.001.004.00042 (Box 4)
  - [Eating Disorder Group, 2 of 2] - eating working group, 1998 -- 2000; UA156.001.004.00043 (Box 4)
  - Issues / topics [1 of 4] - women and war - Afghanistan, 2001; UA156.001.004.00044 (Box 4)
  - Issues / topics [2 of 4] - Women and science, 1999; UA156.001.004.00045 (Box 4)
  - Issues / topics [3 of 4] - Women and sports / Sherman, 1999; UA156.001.004.00046 (Box 4)
  - Issues / topics [4 of 4] - engineering, 1999; UA156.001.004.00047 (Box 4)
  - Greek issues, 2003; UA156.001.004.00048 (Box 4)
  - Activism articles, 2003; UA156.001.004.00049 (Box 4)
  - Mentoring programs, 2000 -- 2003; UA156.001.004.00050 (Box 4)
  - Whiteness / theory / overall, 1999; UA156.001.004.00051 (Box 4)
  - Civil society / community, 2000 -- 2001; UA156.001.004.00052 (Box 4)
  - Anti-racism work, 2000; UA156.001.004.00053 (Box 4)
  - Committees [1 of 5] - women's studies, 2004 -- 2005; UA156.001.004.00054 (Box 4)
  - Committees [2 of 5 - Equal Educational Opportunity Committee], 2002 -- 2003; UA156.001.004.00055 (Box 4)
  - Committees [3 of 5] - women's studies faculty list, 2001 -- 2002; UA156.001.004.00056 (Box 4)
  - Committees [4 of 5] - staff meetings, 2001; UA156.001.004.00057 (Box 4)
  - Committees [5 of 5] - bias intervention, 2002 -- 2003; UA156.001.004.00058 (Box 4)
  - Procedure C protocols [Student Sexual Assault Response Assistance manual], 2003; UA156.001.004.00059 (Box 4)
  - Boston area college sexual assault, 2004; UA156.001.004.00060 (Box 4)
  - Undergraduate experience taskforce, 2002; UA156.001.004.00061 (Box 4)
  - Study abroad issues, 2000 -- 2001; UA156.001.004.00062 (Box 4)
  - Self-study / accreditation, 2001; UA156.001.004.00063 (Box 4)
  - Speaker series on race, 1999 -- 2000; UA156.001.004.00064 (Box 4)
  - Police liaison program, 2000 -- 2001; UA156.001.004.00065 (Box 4)
  - Tom Penichter, 2004 -- 2005; UA156.001.004.00066 (Box 4)
  - Programs abroad directors, 2000; UA156.001.004.00067 (Box 4)
  - Diversity funding, 2000 -- 2002; UA156.001.004.00068 (Box 4)
  - [Symposiums, 1 of 2] - diversity sym., 2002 -- 2003; UA156.001.004.00069 (Box 4)
  - [Symposiums, 2 of 2] - Education for Public Inquiry and International Citizenship, 1999 -- 2000; UA156.001.004.00070 (Box 4)
  - [Equal Education Opportunity Committee], 1997; UA156.001.004.00071 (Box 4)
  - Class teams, 2000; UA156.001.004.00072 (Box 4)
  - [American College Personnel Association], 2001; UA156.001.004.00073 (Box 4)
  - Women's studies, 1997 -- 2003; UA156.001.004.00074 (Box 4)
  - Women's studies internships, 1998 -- 1999; UA156.001.004.00075 (Box 4)
  - [Office of Equal Opportunity] training, 1999; UA156.001.004.00076 (Box 4)
  - [Sexual Assault and Response Program], 1999; UA156.001.004.00077 (Box 4)
  - Administrators - diversity, 1996 -- 1998; UA156.001.004.00078 (Box 4)
  - [Student Services] desk, 2000; UA156.001.004.00079 (Box 4)
  - LGB stuff, 1994 -- 1999; UA156.001.004.00080 (Box 4)
  - Museum School, 1999; UA156.001.004.00081 (Box 4)
  - [Association of Tufts Alumnae], 1997 -- 1999; UA156.001.004.00082 (Box 4)
  - Other [1 of 3] - ACT Roxbury, 2001; UA156.001.004.00083 (Box 4)
  - Other [2 of 3] - Girls LEAP stationary, 2000; UA156.001.004.00084 (Box 4)
  - Other [3 of 3] - respond, 1999; UA156.001.004.00085 (Box 4)
  - Gay and Lesbian Defense Committee, 1986; UA156.001.004.00086 (Box 4)
  - Ann Robinson, 1999; UA156.001.004.00087 (Box 4)
  - Staff retreat, 2002; UA156.001.004.00088 (Box 4)
  - Time line, 2000 -- 2002; UA156.001.004.00089 (Box 4)
  - Campus violence - sororities, 2003; UA156.001.004.00090 (Box 4)
  - Peer education retreat, 1998; UA156.001.004.00091 (Box 4)
  - Peer education training, 1998; UA156.001.004.00092 (Box 4)
  - Peer education training - general, 1998; UA156.001.004.00093 (Box 4)
  - Body image history, 1998; UA156.001.004.00094 (Box 4)
  - Body image workshop ideas, 1997 -- 1998; UA156.001.004.00095 (Box 4)
  - Cultural concepts [body image workshop], 1997; UA156.001.004.00096 (Box 4)
  - [Poems], 1997; UA156.001.004.00097 (Box 4)
  - Relationships [1 of 3], 1984 -- 1989; UA156.001.004.00098 (Box 4)
  - Relationships [2 of 3], 1993; UA156.001.004.00099 (Box 4)
  - Relationships [3 of 3] white copies fall, 1997; UA156.001.004.00100 (Box 4)
  - [Rape education, 1 of 2] - orientation, rape ed, forms / schedules, 1998; UA156.001.004.00101 (Box 4)
  - [Rape education, 2 of 2] - rape / sexual assault - definitions, 1997; UA156.001.004.00102 (Box 4)
  - Violence, 1992 -- 1998; UA156.001.004.00103 (Box 4)
  - Brochure ideas, 1990; UA156.001.004.00104 (Box 4)
  - Internship information, 1997 -- 1998; UA156.001.005.00001 (Box 5)
  - Intern S, 1997; UA156.001.005.00002 (Box 5)
    Contains student course papers.
  - Internship information, 1994; UA156.001.005.00003 (Box 5)
  - To buy, 1997; UA156.001.005.00004 (Box 5)
  - [WNMN] - facilitator training, 2000; UA156.001.005.00005 (Box 5)
  - In the Sack - ex-college, 2004; UA156.001.005.00006 (Box 5)
  - In the Sack - evaluation, 2003; UA156.001.005.00007 (Box 5)
  - In the Sack - feedback, 2003; UA156.001.005.00008 (Box 5)
  - In the Sack - program, 2003; UA156.001.005.00009 (Box 5)
  - In the Sack - survivor's stories, 2003; UA156.001.005.00010 (Box 5)
  - Rebecca Butler, 2003; UA156.001.005.00011 (Box 5)
  - In the Sack - logistics, 2003; UA156.001.005.00012 (Box 5)
  - In the Sack - training, 2003; UA156.001.005.00013 (Box 5)
  - Statistics / In the Sack training, 2003; UA156.001.005.00014 (Box 5)
  - In the Sack - manual, 2002 -- 2003; UA156.001.005.00015 (Box 5)
  - In the Sack - facilitator information, 2003; UA156.001.005.00016 (Box 5)
  - Rape Education Program 2003, UA156.001.005.00017 (Box 5)
  - In the Sack - 2005, UA156.001.005.00018 (Box 5)
  - [Orientation program], 2004; UA156.001.005.00019 (Box 5)
  - In the Sack - accounts, 2004; UA156.001.005.00020 (Box 5)
  - In the Sack - program, 2004; UA156.001.005.00021 (Box 5)
  - In the Sack - session schedules, 2004; UA156.001.005.00022 (Box 5)
  - In the Sack - manual, 2004; UA156.001.005.00023 (Box 5)
  - [Date rape drugs], 2004; UA156.001.005.00024 (Box 5)
  - In the Sack - slides, 2004; UA156.001.005.00025 (Box 5)
  - In the Sack - small groups, 2004; UA156.001.005.00026 (Box 5)
  - In the Sack - observers, 2004; UA156.001.005.00027 (Box 5)
  - In the Sack - staff comments, 2004; UA156.001.005.00028 (Box 5)
  - In the Sack - logistics, 2004; UA156.001.005.00029 (Box 5)
  - In the Sack - speaker, 2004; UA156.001.005.00030 (Box 5)
  - In the Sack - manual, 2003; UA156.001.005.00031 (Box 5)
  - WNMN - In the Sack revisions, 2003; UA156.001.005.00032 (Box 5)
  - WNMN - students [1 of 3] - blank forms, 2002; UA156.001.005.00033 (Box 5)
  - WNMN - students [2 of 3] - dinner, 2001 -- 2002; UA156.001.005.00034 (Box 5)
  - WNMN - students [3 of 5] - WNMN, 2002 -- 2003; UA156.001.005.00035 (Box 5)
  - WNMN - evaluations, 1994; UA156.001.005.00036 (Box 5)
  - [WNMN] - advertising, 2001; UA156.001.005.00037 (Box 5)
  - WNMN - summer letters, 2001; UA156.001.005.00038 (Box 5)
  - WNMN - students, 2002; UA156.001.005.00039 (Box 5)
  - WNMN - student information, 2001; UA156.001.005.00040 (Box 5)
  - [WNMN] - facilitators / actors, 2001; UA156.001.005.00041 (Box 5)
  - [WNMN] - student information F, 2000; UA156.001.005.00042 (Box 5)
  - [WNMN] - Sac / actors, 1999; UA156.001.005.00043 (Box 5)
  - [WNMN] - Yahoo, 2002; UA156.001.005.00044 (Box 5)
  - [WNMN] - definitions of rape, 2000 -- 2003; UA156.001.005.00045 (Box 5)
  - WNMN - sign up for programs, 2002; UA156.001.005.00046 (Box 5)
  - WNMN [facilitation, 1 of 3] - handout, 2002; UA156.001.005.00047 (Box 5)
  - WNMN [facilitation, 2 of 3] - script for moderators, 2002; UA156.001.005.00048 (Box 5)
  - WNMN [facilitation, 3 of 3] - guide, 2002; UA156.001.005.00049 (Box 5)
  - WNMN program [1 of 4], 2000 -- 2002; UA156.001.005.00050 (Box 5)
  - WMNM program [2 of 4] - format, 2000; UA156.001.005.00051 (Box 5)
  - WNMN program [3 of 4] - discussion groups, 2000; UA156.001.005.00052 (Box 5)
  - WNMN - program [4 of 4] - information for moderators, 1998; UA156.001.005.00053 (Box 5)
  - WNMN - summer reading, 2000; UA156.001.005.00054 (Box 5)
  - WNMN - Liz's handout, 2000; UA156.001.005.00055 (Box 5)
  - [WNMN] - scenarios revised, 1999 -- 2000; UA156.001.005.00056 (Box 5)
  - Rape education orientation scenario, 1999; UA156.001.005.00057 (Box 5)
  - WNMN - questions in character, 2000; UA156.001.005.00058 (Box 5)
  - WNMN - questions for actors, 2000; UA156.001.005.00059 (Box 5)
  - WNMN - staff comments, 2002; UA156.001.005.00060 (Box 5)
  - [WNMN - feedback], 2001; UA156.001.005.00061 (Box 5)
  - [WNMN] - staff comments F, 1999; UA156.001.005.00062 (Box 5)
  - WNMN slides [1 of 3], 2001 -- 2002; UA156.001.005.00063 (Box 5)
    - Rape Education Slides (20) orientation, 2001 -- 2002; UA156.001.005.00063.00001
    - Why No Means No 1, 2001; UA156.001.005.00063.00002
  - WNMN slides [2 of 3], 2002; UA156.001.005.00064 (Box 5)
  - WNMN slides [3 of 3], 2002; UA156.001.005.00065 (Box 5)
  - WNMN logistics [1 of 5], 2002; UA156.001.005.00066 (Box 5)
  - WNMN logistics [2 of 5], 2001; UA156.001.005.00067 (Box 5)
  - WNMN logistics [3 of 5] - F, 2000; UA156.001.005.00068 (Box 5)
  - WNMN logistics [4 of 5] - F, 1999; UA156.001.005.00069 (Box 5)
  - WNMN logistics [5 of 5] - Rape education orientation, 1997 -- 1998; UA156.001.005.00070 (Box 5)
  - [WNMN] - Fall, 1998; UA156.001.005.00071 (Box 5)
  - NECSAN presentation, 1997; UA156.001.005.00072 (Box 5)
  - NECSAN transparencies, 1997; UA156.001.005.00073 (Box 5)
  - Grant 1 presentation, 1997; UA156.001.005.00074 (Box 5)
  - Grant presentation 1, 1997; UA156.001.005.00075 (Box 5)
  - AWARE, 1998 -- 1999; UA156.001.005.00076 (Box 5)
  - AWARE booklet, 1993 -- 1994; UA156.001.005.00077 (Box 5)
  - AWARE booklet - personal, 1994; UA156.001.005.00078 (Box 5)
  - NECSAN work, 1999 -- 2000; UA156.001.005.00079 (Box 5)
  - [Sexual assault program coordinators], 2000; UA156.001.005.00080 (Box 5)
  - [Vagina Monologues programs], 2005 -- 2006; UA156.001.005.00081 (Box 5)
  - [International Women's Day - Nigeria posters], 2004; UA156.001.005.00082 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 3)
  - [Vulvapalooza banner], 2005; UA156.001.010.00001 (Box 10)
  - [Vday tank top], 2005; UA156.001.010.00002 (Box 10)
  - [Peggy Barrett's office sign], 2000; UA156.001.010.00003 (Box 10)
    Sign reads: Peggy Barrett, Director, Women's Programs.
  - Women's Center Governing Board -- Good Idea Notebook, UA156.001.011.00001 (Box 11)
  - Women's Studies @ Tufts, UA156.001.011.00002 (Box 11)
  - EER (?) Educator Binder, UA156.001.011.00003 (Box 11)
  - Domestic Violence, Assault, Harassment (Binder), UA156.001.011.00004 (Box 11)
  - Web Central (Binder), 2005; UA156.001.011.00005 (Box 11)
  - Orientation, 2003 -- 2004; UA156.001.011.00006 (Box 11)
  - Orientation, 2002 -- 2003; UA156.001.011.00007 (Box 11)
  - Rape Education Program (Why No Means No), Orientation, 2002; UA156.001.011.00008 (Box 11)
  - Orientation, 2001 -- 2002; UA156.001.011.00009 (Box 11)
  - Orientation, 2000 -- 2001; UA156.001.011.00010 (Box 11)
  - Orientation, 1999 -- 2000; UA156.001.011.00011 (Box 11)
  - Orientation, 1998 -- 1999; UA156.001.011.00012 (Box 11)
  - Women's Center, 2003 -- 2004; UA156.001.011.00013 (Box 11)
  - Women's Center, 2002 -- 2003; UA156.001.011.00014 (Box 11)
  - Women's Center, 2001 -- 2002; UA156.001.011.00015 (Box 11)
  - Women's Center, 1999 -- 2000; UA156.001.011.00016 (Box 11)
  - Women's Programs, 1998 -- 1999; UA156.001.011.00017 (Box 11)
  - Women's Programs, 1997 -- 1998; UA156.001.011.00018 (Box 11)
  - Women's Programs, 1996 -- 1997; UA156.001.011.00019 (Box 11)
  - Women's Programs, 1995 -- 1996; UA156.001.011.00020 (Box 11)
  - Memoribilia, etc., UA156.001.011.00021 (Box 11)
  - Women's Programs, 1994 -- 1995; UA156.001.011.00022 (Box 11)
  - Women's Programs, 1993 -- 1994; UA156.001.011.00023 (Box 11)
  - WC Events History (Folder 1 of 5), 1975 -- 1981; UA156.001.012.00001 (Box 12)
  - WC Events History (Folder 2 of 5), 1975 -- 1981; UA156.001.012.00002 (Box 12)
  - WC Events History (Folder 3 of 5), 1975 -- 1981; UA156.001.012.00003 (Box 12)
  - WC Events History (Folder 4 of 5), 1975 -- 1981; UA156.001.012.00004 (Box 12)
  - WC Events History (Folder 5 of 5), 1975 -- 1981; UA156.001.012.00005 (Box 12)
  - WC Events History (Folder 1 of 4), 1981 -- 1988; UA156.001.012.00006 (Box 12)
  - WC Events History (Folder 2 of 4), 1981 -- 1988; UA156.001.012.00007 (Box 12)
  - WC Events History (Folder 3 of 4), 1981 -- 1988; UA156.001.012.00008 (Box 12)
  - WC Events History (Folder 4 of 4) Back Matter, 1981 -- 1988; UA156.001.012.00009 (Box 12)
  - WC Events History (Folder 1 of 3), 1988 -- 1996; UA156.001.012.00010 (Box 12)
  - WC Events History (Folder 2 of 3), 1988 -- 1996; UA156.001.012.00011 (Box 12)
  - WC Events History (Folder 3 of 3), 1988 -- 1996; UA156.001.012.00012 (Box 12)
  - WC Events History (Folder 1 of 4), 1996 -- 2003; UA156.001.012.00013 (Box 12)
  - WC Events History (Folder 2 of 4), 1996 -- 2003; UA156.001.012.00014 (Box 12)
  - WC Events History (Folder 3 of 4), 1996 -- 2003; UA156.001.012.00015 (Box 12)
  - WC Events History (Folder 4 of 4), 1996 -- 2003; UA156.001.012.00016 (Box 12)
  - WC Events History, 2003 -- 2007; UA156.001.012.00017 (Box 12)
  - Binder, UA156.001.012.00018 (Box 12)
  - Programming Ideas, Women's Center (Folder 1 of 6) Front Matter, 2004 -- 2005; UA156.001.012.00019 (Box 12)
  - Programming Ideas, Women's Center (Folder 2 of 6), 2004 -- 2005; UA156.001.012.00020 (Box 12)
  - Programming Ideas, Women's Center (Folder 3 of 6), 2004 -- 2005; UA156.001.012.00021 (Box 12)
  - Programming Ideas, Women's Center (Folder 4 of 6), 2004 -- 2005; UA156.001.012.00022 (Box 12)
  - Programming Ideas, Women's Center (Folder 5 of 6), 2004 -- 2005; UA156.001.012.00023 (Box 12)
  - Programming Ideas, Women's Center (Folder 6 of 6), 2004 -- 2005; UA156.001.012.00024 (Box 12)
  - Domestic Violence/Background Information (Folder 1 of 4) Front Matter, UA156.001.012.00025 (Box 12)
  - Domestic Violence/Background Information (Folder 2 of 4), UA156.001.012.00026 (Box 12)
  - Domestic Violence/Background Information (Folder 3 of 4), UA156.001.012.00027 (Box 12)
  - Domestic Violence/Background Information (Folder 4 of 4), UA156.001.012.00028 (Box 12)
  - Women's Center office files, UA156.000675; 2 Digital Object(s) 2 zip disks (Box Shared Digital Media 1)
- Log books, 1974 -- 2001; UA156.002; 2.4 Linear Feet; 1 Volumes
  This series contains the Women's Center log books, from 1974 through 1987. These logs were notebooks in which Women's Center staff recorded information about the day's activities, upcoming events, and notes to other staff members. Occasionally staff inserted relevant news clippings, fliers or correspondence into the log books. Also included at the end of the series is a notebook containing event fliers, approximately dating from 1996 to 2001. On April 2, 1977, the Women's Center suffered a fire in their office on the second floor of Curtis Hall. The four log books that predate the fire were somewhat water damaged before arriving at DCA; the 1974-1975 log book, which was severely damaged, is stored separately.
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  - [Log book], 1975-04 -- 1975-12; UA156.002.005.00083 (Box 5)
    This log book was slightly water damaged before arriving at DCA. See series description.
  - [Log book], 1975-10 -- 1976-04; UA156.002.005.00084 (Box 5)
  - [Log book], 1976-12 -- 1977-04-02; UA156.002.005.00085 (Box 5)
  - [Log book], 1977-04 -- 1977-11; UA156.002.005.00086 (Box 5)
  - [Log book], 1974 -- 1975; UA156.002.005.00087 (Box 5)
    This log book was water damaged before arriving at DCA. See series description. It is being stored separately for preservation purposes. The front cover and one interior page are particularly deteriorated. DCA staff have put the cover in a Mylar enclosure and photocopied both the cover and the interior page.
  - [Log book], 1977-11 -- 1978-05; UA156.002.006.00001 (Box 6)
  - [Log book], 1978-09 -- 1979-01; UA156.002.006.00002 (Box 6)
  - [Log book], 1979-01 -- 1979-11; UA156.002.006.00003 (Box 6)
  - [Log book], 1979-10 -- 1980-02; UA156.002.006.00004 (Box 6)
  - [Log book], 1980-03 -- 1980-10; UA156.002.006.00005 (Box 6)
  - [Log book], 1980-10 -- 1981-03; UA156.002.006.00006 (Box 6)
  - [Log book], 1981-04; UA156.002.006.00007 (Box 6)
  - [Log book], 1981-03 -- 1982-01; UA156.002.006.00008 (Box 6)
  - [Log book], 1982-01 -- 1982-11; UA156.002.006.00009 (Box 6)
  - [Log book], 1982-11 -- 1983-12; UA156.002.006.00010 (Box 6)
  - [Log book], 1984-01 -- 1984-12; UA156.002.006.00011 (Box 6)
  - [Log book], 1985-01 -- 1987-04; UA156.002.006.00012 (Box 6)
  - [Book of fliers], 1996 -- 2001; UA156.002.006.00013 (Box 6)
- Publications, pamphlets, and women's organizations, 1964 -- 2010; UA156.003; 4.1 Linear Feet
  This series contains journals, magazines, reports, handbooks and pamphlets, dating from 1964 to 2010. Most of these materials relate to women's issues, some to LGBT or minority concerns with particular emphasis on women's health as well as feminist literature. The majority of the material was produced by non-Tufts organizations.
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  - The abortion business: A report on free-standing abortion clinics, 1975; UA156.003.006.00014; Archiprete, Kaye; Garbarino, Paula; Popkin, Maggi; Rosenberg, Debby; Sassen, Georgia (Box 6)
    A publication of the Women's Research Action Project